Stab me through the heart if it's what you want
If someone as unreliable as me could become something someday
I'll become a dream so bright
It will fill the night with tears that flow on their own
My foggy breath glistens for a moment
Before it fades into the cold of winter
Just like the warmth from the time we laid hands on each other
It was all too unberable
There was a time when
I thought that spring would always come as a matter of course
A time when I believed that all dreams come true
Fly me to the stars if it's what you want
If someone as spineless as me could one day find meaning in life
I'll become a dream so intense
It will blend love and hate and never let you wake up
Let us head outside under the frozen night sky
Wrapped together in the warmth of your coat
There was a time when
I thought that you would always be by my side as a matter of course
Now I don't want to lose them
Even if this rain of memories sinks into my wounds
Stab me through the heart if it's what you want
If someone as unreliable as me could become something someday
I'll become a dream so bright
It will fill the night with tears that flow on their own
I'll dive into the sea of memories
And pick up the pieces of our love
I'll hide you in them forever
To make my world a little brighter
Even if our love becomes a curse too much to bear
Eating away at me bit by bit, day by day
You will still be the one in the depths of my heart
We'll find each other and become one
Fading into the dream
Stab me through the heart if it's what you want
If someone as unreliable as me could become something someday
I'll become a dream so bright
It will fill the night with tears that flow on their own
The dream I'll have tonight
Will it come true or not, I don't know