I said don't.
Stop it.
Record: November 2016, Tokyo
Due to persistent bullying by classmates,
four male students, including the leader, suffered grave injuries.
Tokyo
Jujutsu High School
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Special-Grade Cursed Human Okkotsu Yuta
Special-Grade Cursed Apparition Orimoto Rika
Record: Six Years Ago, Sendai City, Miyagi Prefecture
Tokyo Jujutsu High School              [Student ID]
Special
Student ID #
Name         Okkotsu Yuta
DOB: 03/07/2001
This is proof that the individual listed above is a student.
Sexy Talk
Every Tues/Fri get a 5x Point Bonus!
Authorized Personnel Only
No Trespassing
We're
closed.
Throat Remedy
Danger!
No Service
Enter Your Passcode
Tokyo Jujutsu High School                [Student ID]
Special
Student ID #
Name            Okkotsu Yuta
DOB: 03/07/2001
This is proof that the individual listed above is a student.
Death to Fools
Punishment to the Weak
Love to the Strong
Death to
Punishment to
Love to
Kabuki Town, First Street
December 24th, Day of the Night Parade of a Hundred Demons
Record: December 24th, 2017
Special-Grade Cursed Apparition, Orimoto Rika
Fully Manifested a Second Time
Theatrical Release
JUJUTSU KAISEN