It's been a while, Okkotsu.
Stay away.
Oh, come on. Don't play hard to get.
You can't.
Do you know how much I've wanted to punch you?
Try to understand my feelings!
Right?
Stop it.
If you keep me on edge like this, I might just end up killing you.
Don't do it, Rika!
Rika?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You want to cover up the incident
and have the boy be executed in secret?
That's ridiculous.
The boy himself has consented to it.
He's underage. Just sixteen years old.
We don't know how many might curse to death.
He has already turned the tables on
three second-grades and even a first-grade.
That's why you've turned to me.
Have you forgotten that?
Then you're suggesting...
Indeed.
We'll be taking Okkotsu Yuta into Jujutsu Tech.
Do you mind explaining what this is, Okkotsu Yuta?
It's a knife... or at least it used to be.
I tried to kill myself...
but Rika wouldn't let me.
That's dark.
You're starting at a new school today.
I'm not going.
I don't want to hurt anyone anymore.
So I'm never going outside again.
But you know...
It gets lonely all by yourself.
Depending on how it's used,
the curse placed on you can save people as well.
Learn to use that power.
After that, you're free to decide
whether it's worth throwing everything away.
Did you hear about the transfer student starting today?
They say he "stuffed" four of his classmates into a locker.
He killed them?
Tuna mayo?
Nope, but gravely injured, apparently.
Well, if he's too cocky, I'll put him in his place.
Bonito flakes.
Listen up, everyone! Transfer student! Incoming!
Let's all give him a hand!
Not one hand...
I heard he's a real wet blanket.
Hard to get excited about welcoming someone like that.
Salmon.
Moving on!
Come on in!
I sense a really damp mood in there.
I'll just ignore him.
I'm Okkotsu Yut—
Is this some kind of test?
Hey.
You're cursed.
This is a place to learn about curses.
Not a place for the cursed to be.
Huh?
More than ten thousand unexplained deaths and
missing persons are reported annually across the country.
Most of them are a result of curses
born from the negative emotions of people.
Among them are also some malicious cases caused by curse users.
You need curses to fight curses.
And this is where we learn about curses to exorcise curses:
Tokyo Jujutsu Technical High School.
You're just telling me that now?
You're just telling him that now?
My bad!
Oh, I'd back away real quick if I were you.
Do not...
Wait! Rika!
...bully Yuta!
Over there! Check it out!
What is it?
Happy birthday, Yuta.
Whoa! Can I open it?
Go ahead.
Really? I can open it?!
Just do it already!
Wow!
A ring?
It's an engagement ring.
What's engagement?
It's a promise.
A promise that when we grow up, we'll get married.
Is this real?!
Hey! Someone call an ambulance!
Idiot! Just look at her! It's too late!
Are they okay?
What happened?
Her head's crushed in!
But still...
A child got run over by a car! Yes! Hurry!
Help them!
I'm not going near that!
Rika?
Yuta...
Yuta.
When we grow up,
we'll get married!
It's a promise.
So as you see, he's cursed by Rika,
who is madly in love with him!
Let's welcome Okkotsu Yuta!
Be nice to him, everyone!
Remember that attacking Yuta will activate Rika's curse.
Or maybe it won't. Hard to say.
Either way, be careful!
Should've said it sooner.
Since they're being so rebellious,
I'll just make some quick introductions.
I have a feeling this teacher is the problem.
This is the cursed tool user, Zenin Maki.
She uses special tools to exorcise curses.
This is the cursed speech user, Inumaki Toge.
He can only speak in rice ball ingredients,
so good luck talking to him!
Kelp.
This is Panda.
I'm Panda.
Nice to meet you.
Well, there you have it.
He didn't give me the explanation I wanted most!
All right! Our first-year class is a solid four students!
Three students and one animal, anyway.
For your afternoon jujutsu practice,
you'll be working in pairs.
Toge and Panda, pair up.
Let's do this.
Maki and Yuta, pair up.
Yikes!
Did she just say "yikes"?!
U-Um, I-I hope we can work together.
You were bullied, weren't you?
Thought so.
I totally get it. Even I'd bully you.
Maybe you do it because of the curse,
but that good guy act you got plastered all over your face, it's disgusting.
Why are you playing the victim
when you're the one being protected?
I bet you've been passive your whole life.
You think you can get by just like that?
You're underestimating Jujutsu Tech.
That's enough, Maki.
Bonito flakes!
All right, fine. Get off my case.
Sorry about that.
She has a habit of making assumptions about people.
It's fine.
She's not wrong.
Where are we?
It's just an elementary school.
Oh?
Just another elementary school where kids have gone missing.
Wait, what?!
It happens in places like this.
Probably the handiwork of a naturally occurring curse.
You're saying they were kidnapped by a curse?
Yup, two that we know of.
Curses tend to manifest in crowded places
that many people have memories of.
Places like schools and hospitals which
are often remembered with negative emotions
are likely to form pools of negative energy.
As those emotions build up,
they give birth to curses like the one here.
Exorcise the curse. Rescue the children.
And retrieve them if they're dead.
They could be dead?
Emerge from the darkness that is darker than black.
Purify that which is impure.
It's getting dark!
It's a Veil.
It's a barrier that will smoke out the curse
and keep you guys concealed from the outside world.
You can easily undo it from the inside!
Now, do be careful not to die on us.
R-Really?
Wait, Sir!
Hey, transfer student.
Don't get distracted.
Put... me... on?
Put me on?
T-They're coming this way!
Wh-Wh-What do we do?!
Be quiet.
Here's a lesson for you.
The weaker they are,
the more they tend to group together.
Though, I guess it's the same for humans.
Incredible...
With just one swing!
Come on, let's move it.
Huh? Where to?
Inside, obviously.
Aren't you scared, Zenin?
Don't use my last name.
S-Sorry...
It's just... it feels like this place is haunted!
It's like we're being watched.
Not a lot of curses here
even though the Veil's been drawn.
No, they are here. They just aren't attacking.
Is it because he's here?
S-Something just moved!
Hey!
Yes?!
What grade are you?
Um, like in English proficiency?
Sorcerers are ranked in grades one through four.
But I only started at Jujutsu Tech this week.
I don't think I'm ranked yet.
Ugh, forget it.
Just show me your student ID.
You got one from that blindfolded dumbass, right?
Blindfolded dumbass...
Yes, here you go.
Well, if you joined with no prior history,
you're probably a fourth-grade.
Special grade?!
That means he's even higher than first grade?
This has to be some kind of joke!
Um, Zenin...
Zenin! Zenin!
Behind you.
Shit!
A little too big, aren't ya?!
Take this, you bastard!
Thank, thank, thanks for the meal.
Damn it, damn it!
I dropped my cursed tool!
Let us outta here, goddammit!
Where are we?
Inside that curse's stomach!
You shouldn't be passing out over this.
You mean it ate us?!
Damn right!
Where's that curse of yours when we need it?!
Even I don't know what makes Rika come out!
More importantly, what do we do now?!
We can expect help sometime after the Veil is lifted.
It's so embarrassing, damn it!
Help!
Huh?
Please! He's about to die!
You're saying they were kidnapped by a curse?
Yup, two that we know of.
Exorcise the curse. Rescue the children.
And retrieve them if they're dead.
Thank goodness they're alive.
No, it's not good.
Take a closer look.
The big one's obviously been affected by the curse, too.
Both of them could die at any moment.
No way...
What do we do?!
There's nothing we can do!
We have no choice but to wait for help.
Not everyone has resistance to curses like you.
Zenin?
Zenin?!
What's this wound?
Is it the curse?
Is she going to die?
Please, save us, mister!
Please!
You keep asking, but I can't—
Okkotsu!
Why the hell did you even come to Jujutsu Tech?!
What do you want?!
What are your goals?!
What are you trying to achieve?!
I just... don't want to see anyone getting hurt again.
I tried to lock myself away and disappear.
But I was told it'd be lonely being all by myself,
and I couldn't argue.
I want to interact!
I want to be needed!
I want to know that it's okay for me to be alive!
Then start exorcising.
Exorcise curses and keep on exorcising them!
The confidence and interactions you want
will all come to you in due time!
That's just the kind of place Jujutsu Tech is.
Rika.
What's up?
Lend me your strength.
Who are you?
Be quiet!
Now that's terrifying.
So the special-grade vengeful spirit, Orimoto Rika, has fully manifested.
Oh my, how freaky.
Wow!
So pretty!
I'm so pretty!
I love it!
Hang on, everyone!
Just a little more!
I need to hurry and get them to Teacher.
I hope Rika keeps the curse distracted until then.
Don't fall now!
Not yet!
I've decided it's about time. I'm gonna change.
You can do it, Yuta.
I will!
Welcome back.
You did well.
They say both Maki and the kids will be fine.
That's a relief.
You don't look too relieved.
I managed to call out Rika for the first time.
Really? That's a big step forward.
One, two...
Slow down, Yuta!
I said slow down!
Chill out, Rika!
There! Take that!
It's a promise.
When we grow up, we'll get married.
Sure!
Then we'll be together forever and ever!
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
I just remembered something.
I'm starting to think Rika didn't curse me.  cursed me.}
I think I might have cursed Rika instead.
This is just a personal opinion,
but love is the most twisted curse of all.
Sir, I've decided.
I'll learn all I can at Jujutsu Tech and break Rika's curse.
The special-grade vengeful spirit,
Orimoto Rika, was fully manifested for 422 seconds.
We entrusted you with Okkotsu precisely to prevent situations like this.
There is no room for excuses, Gojo Satoru.
Well, I never really planned on making any.
How dare you take this lightly?!
Had Orimoto Rika's rampage continued, an entire town could have been wiped out!
I would've risked my life to stop that.
But there's only one word I'd use to describe this curse:
Incomprehensible.
How did this girl,
who has no history of sorcery in her family,
become such an immensely strong curse?
You can't control what you don't understand.
So it's gonna take some trial and error.
Just leave it alone for a while.
Do not forget that Okkotsu's
execution was merely suspended.
And don't you forget
if it comes down to that, I'll side with Okkotsu.
Christ, I can't stand these arrogant old-timers.
I don't ever wanna turn out like them.
I gotta be careful.
Besides, no one's allowed to take youth away from the young.
Last lap for Maki and Toge!
Absolutely no one.
All right, go ahead.
Oh, sure.
A curse as strong as Orimoto Rika
is pretty much impossible to exorcise.
Breaking it, however, is a totally different story.
Analyze the tens of thousands of knots
of cursed energy and unravel them one by one.
It's something that can only be done
by you—the one who is cursed.
What exactly do I do?
Use this.
A sword?
Curses are most stable when they're possessing something.
Back then, you used the ring to connect to Orimoto Rika.
The pipeline is already there.
You just need to borrow some of Rika's curse,
infuse it into the sword, and control it.
Increase the amount as you repeat it
and eventually, you'll master it.
Do that and you'll be free.
Both you and her.
So I have to channel the curse through the sword...
And there's one more thing!
You need to learn sword fighting as well.
You're super weak, after all.
We're gonna put you through the wringer!
Tuna.
Hey, what's up! How's it going?
Oh, hey—
Don't get distracted.
Right.
Take your stance already, idiot!
Wow, harsh!
Right!
You were gonna score a hit on me, right?
Yes!
She dodged that?!
But she's off-balance!
I'll get her on the landing!
No way!
Congrats, you're dead.
I win again.
Was that last one necessary?
You're getting complacent.
Always treat training like it's a real battle.
Experiencing pain or avoiding it
makes a huge difference in how fast you grow.
That's right. I've...
One more time, please!
I've got to break Rika's curse!
Has it only been three months since Yuta joined us?
He's moving a lot better now.
Salmon.
He's more positive, too.
Salmon roe.
Looks like Maki is having fun as well.
I guess it's because she didn't have anyone to spar with until—
Eureka!
Yuta, get over here! C'mon!
Huh?
What's up, Panda?
We gotta have a super important discussion, so listen closely!
Do you prefer big boobs or small boobs?
Why now?!
I-I've never really given it much thought,
Uh-huh!
but I suppose I prefer them somewhat big?
Oh-ho!
Maki!
What?
You've got a chance!
Chance!
What crazy ideas are you getting? I'll kill you!
Don't be embarrassed. What are you, a kid?
All right, time's up!
The WWF ain't coming to save you here!
What's that all about?
Kelp.
I still don't know much about Inumaki.
I'm a bit scared, to be honest.
Okay, gather round!
You two keep training.
Toge, you've been requested.
It's a curse that's right up your alley.
Go exorcise it quickly.
Salmon.
Requested?
Toge's the only second-grade sorcerer among us first years.
He even gets solo missions from time to time!
Wow, that's impressive.
You're special-grade for god's sake.
Yuta, you'll be going with him as support.
Oh, I'm supporting him?
Well, you're more of an observer, really.
The types of sorcery are many and varied.
There are as many ways to exorcise as there are sorcerers.
Toge's cursed speech is a good example.
Try to learn all you can from him.
What is cursed speech?
As the term suggests,
it involves infusing sound with cursed energy.
Don't worry, it'll make sense when you see it.
To break a curse, you must first understand curses.
It's my first real mission.
Actually, maybe second?
I'm so nervous!
Salmon.
Oh, I-I'm sorry...
Got a minute, Yuta?
Yes?
Sorry, I won't be able to supervise this time.
But this mission is easy enough for Toge
to handle on his own, so you can take it easy.
There's just one thing you need to be careful about:
Don't let Rika out.
There's no guarantee she'll go back like last time.
Use only as much of Rika's power as you can through the sword.
If she were to manifest again...
Would that be a problem?
You and I will both be disposed of!
I'm counting on you!
Why drop the bomb on me right now?!
We've arrived.
This is the Hapina Shopping District.
Most of the shops have closed down by now.
There are plans to demolish the
entire area and build a shopping mall.
During an inspection of the area,
we confirmed a pack of low-level curses.
We'd like to request for the second-grade sorcerer, Inumaki, to exorcise them.
Wait, where is Inumaki?
Not here?
Thanks for the purchase!
Oh, Mr. Ijichi, he's over there.
He went shopping?
What did you buy?
Throat medicine?
Essentially, it would cause issues down the road
if the building they're
spending so much on had a bad history.
Hence the request for an exorcism now.
Salmon.
Then allow me to cast the Veil.
Good luck.
He said it was a pack of low-level curses, right?
Pollack roe.
That's not fair, Mom.
Why does he get more?
So what? Let's trade that for a new one!
I smell olives.
I wanna eat sushi!
We have a lost child.
Cheap stuff! Cheap stuff!
It's not scary if we all cross it together.
The weaker they are,
the more they tend to group together.
Even so, there are just too many of them!
Inumaki?!
It could be dangerous if you get too close!
Explode.
Was that cursed speech?
Huh? We're done already?
Tuna mayo.
His voice totally went hoarse!
Oh, that explains the throat medicine.
That's an incredible power,
but it comes with a good deal of risk, too.
Bonito flakes.
What's wrong?
Oh, you're right. The Veil isn't lifting.
Huh?
Looks like we can't get out.
This curse... there's something different about its presence.
Zomba.
Inumaki!
Twist!
Wh-Wha-What is that?!
That curse...
He said they'd be low-level!
This isn't what we were told!
Even though it's smaller,
it's way scarier than the one from the school.
Oh! Inumaki, you're hurt.
Is your finger all right?
Man, that looks painful.
Salmon.
You shouldn't mess with it!
Sorry.
It's my fault.
It doesn't seem to be chasing specifically after us.
I'll contact Mr. Ijichi.
No signal?
But why?
Bonito flakes.
Because of the Veil?
Since the Veil isn't lifting,
we have no choice but to exorcise it, right?
Wait, Inumaki!
Should you be moving around already?
Kelp.
You're going alone?
Thank you, Inumaki.
But I'm all right.
Let's do this together!
Oh?
Go get it, Yuta!
It's getting mad?! Why?!
As if it wasn't scary enough!
Don't look away.
Keep moving.
Infuse the curse into the blade.
Inumaki is actually very kind.
He doesn't want to curse anyone by accident
so he speaks in rice ball ingredients—words that can't carry curses.
He saved me today as well.
Tried to keep me away from danger.
Back when I was nervous,
he was just trying to calm me down, wasn't he?
Zora.
Too shallow. Its skin is so tough!
I'm still no match for this curse.
However...
Inumaki, catch!
I'll make sure to respond to Inumaki's kindness!  's kindness go to waste/be for nothing!}
Get crushed!
Wow!
Mustard leaf!
Oh, I'm fine!
It's only a scratch.
Salmon.
Yeah, we did it!
Once I break Rika's curse,
I'll be a normal person again.
I won't be able to stay at Jujutsu Tech anymore.
But until then, I want to be useful to everyone.
Oh, what do we do about the Veil?
How unfortunate.
I was hoping I'd get to see this rumored Rika.
As fellow special grades, I'm hoping we could get along.
I needed to return something you dropped, too.
Toge's cursed speech, you see,
is something he's been able to use since birth.
Back in the day, he struggled quite a bit.
Sometimes he would curse people by accident.
You two are quite similar in that sense.
That's why he's been thinking of
how to help you since the day you got here.
It's easy to misunderstand him but he's a great guy.
Please continue to be nice to him, okay?
Yeah, I will—
Come on, it's time for training!
Oh, right.
Panda! What are you giggling about?!
Don't make me kill you!
Huh? It's nothing, though.
Um, Maki...
I want to channel cursed energy through my sword more smoothly. Do you know any tricks?
I don't.
Don't ask me about cursed energy.
I scoured every inch of the shopping district and found three different types of residuals.
According to Mr. Ijichi,
the chances of finding anything more are slim.
Okay, got it. Thanks.
You bet!
My apologies.
Our inspection revealed that someone had cast another Veil on top of my own.
Additionally, a semi-first-grade curse made an unexpected appearance.
It's my fault for not being more thorough.
I accept full responsibility for this!
No, it's fine. You were just outclassed.
You mean...
Do you know who is behind this?
Geto Suguru.
Out of the four special-grade sorcerers,
he's the one who was banished from Jujutsu Tech
for cursing over a hundred normal people to death.
He's considered the worst curse user ever.
Really, I'll be fine. Let's go home now.
It's all right. Just wait a little longer.
But...
So, you said your daughter was being haunted by a ghost.
Is that correct, Mrs. Sato?
Ah, yes... um... my name is Saito, though...
No, you are Sato.
Sato is a better name, I decided.
Right...
Mom, let's go home.
But you've been having trouble sleeping lately, right?
This feels like a scam.
You constantly feel a piercing gaze upon you.
Sometimes your shoulders feel heavy and it gets hard to breath, am I right?
Almost as if you've forgotten how.
And you often dream of being violated.
How do you know that?
Don't move.
Huh? No way. I feel much better!
Honestly, I don't know how we could ever repay you.
Please. We must all help each other in times of need.
Feel free to reach out anytime you need.
See, I told you he was simply godly!
Yeah.
Godly, huh?
Aren't you a smart one.
At least for a filthy monkey
who can't even use sorcery.
I can see the real you, Master Geto.
The leaders have all gathered in the meeting room.
What are you doing?
Sanitizing myself.
Can't have that monkey stench infect others.
Man, I'm so happy.
How long has it been since we all gathered?
You know what, since we're all here,
let's take a group photo.
Where's the SLR?
Right here.
Geto! Come out here!
Geto, you bastard!
Well, if it isn't Mr. Kanamori.
What brings you here in such a sweaty panic?
Quit fucking around! Hurry up and exorcise my curse!
Do you know how much I've paid you?!
How much?
Roughly one hundred and five million yen.
No donations for the past six months, however.
W-Well—
Ah, I guess we're done then.
What are you sayi—
Monkeys all have their roles to play.
There are money-collecting monkeys and curse-collecting monkeys.
You're the former.
If you're out of money, I have no further use for you.
Screw you!
Suck, suck... Suck, suck...
Suck, suck, suck, suck...
Disgusting.
Are we really the same species?
That's why I keep saying they're nothing but monkeys.
The time has come, my beloved family.
Let's put an end to the age of monkeys and make the age of sorcerers a reality.
We'll start by sending a declaration to the cornerstone of the world of sorcery—Jujutsu Tech.
A declaration of war.
What's up, Yuta?
Uh, well, I just had a bad premonition.
It's in your head.
Just your imagination.
Bonito flakes.
Really?
Guys, wait!
I mean, your awareness of cursed energy is all whack.
Figures it'd be dulled with something like Rika constantly around.
Tuna.
We still haven't picked up on any actions from Geto.
Are you sure you're not just being paranoid?
I'm sorry, Principal, but I'm sure about this one.
I confirmed it myself on the scene.
There's no way I would mistake Suguru's residuals.
Suguru...
God damn!
Speak of the devil!
Gather all sorcerers, semi-first grade and above, at the front gate!
Wouldn't you know it.
Yuta's intuition was correct.
Salmon.
Doesn't look like a staff member, does it?
Never seen a curse like that before.
Salmon roe.
Wow, that's one big bird!
Still the same as ever.
Whoa, Master Geto, is this really Tokyo?
It's like, so country!
Nanako, that was rude.
Okay? But you totally agree with me,
don't you, Mimiko?
Hurry up and get down already!
Aren't you cold?
Who are they?
Whoa! Look, it's a panda!
It's so cute!
And who are you guys?
Master Yuta won't forgive any intruders.
Kelp!
Wha?
Get lost before you get knocked out by Master Yuta!
Hey!
Nice to meet you, Okkotsu.
I'm Geto Suguru.
He's fast!
Huh? Oh, nice to meet you.
You possess a truly wonderful power, I see.
I believe that great power should be used towards great ends.
Have you ever questioned the current state of the world?
A world where sorcerers are forced to
work in the shadows to protect the order of society.
You see, there's this established paradox
saying the strong must accommodate the weak.
How deplorable!
Uh...
The apex of creation has halted its own evolution!
What nonsense!
It's high time mankind reconsidered its strategy for survival.
Which is why we'd like you to help us.
Help you with what?
We're going to kill all non-sorcerers
and create a world where only sorcerers exist.
What did he...
...say just now?
Could you keep your crazy talk away from my students?
Satoru! Long time no see!
Get away from the kids, Suguru.
I heard this year's freshers were all outstanding.
I see. So they're under your care.
A special-grade cursed human.
A cursed corpse mutation.
A cursed speech user.
And finally,
the Zenin clan's failure.
You piece of...
Careful what you say now.
I don't need a monkey like you in my world.
I'm sorry.
I don't really understand what you're talking about.
But...
I'm not going to help someone who talks down to my friends!
My apologies. It wasn't my intention to upset you.
Then what exactly did you come here for?
To declare war.
To all those gathered here, listen up very closely!
On the coming December 24th, when the sun sets,
the Night Parade of a Hundred Demons will commence!
It will take place in the Crucible of Curses, Shinjuku in Tokyo.
As well as the Holy Land of Jujutsu, Kyoto.
A thousand curses will be unleashed upon each location.
Their sole command, of course, will be to massacre.
If you wish to avoid a scene straight out of hell,
put your lives on the line and fight.
Let us curse each other to our heart's content!
Master Geto!
The café is gonna close!
It's already that late?
I'm sorry, Satoru.
The girls insist on trying the crepes from Takeshita Street.
Hurry!
So I'll be taking my leave now.
Man, I don't get what's so great
about a place filled with monkeys.
What makes you think we'd just let you leave?
You don't wanna do that.
Your precious students are all within my range.
Well then, everyone, see you on the battlefield.
Survival of the weakest.
That's the ideal form society should take.
Help the weak and discourage the strong.
Listen, Satoru.
Sorcerers exist to protect non-sorcerers.
That's your argument?
God, I hate all that righteousness.
Are you the strongest because you're Gojo Satoru?
Or are you Gojo Satoru because you're the strongest?
What exactly are you trying to say?
If I could become you, then wouldn't my foolish ideals become reasonable possibilities?
I've already decided on the path I want to take.
All that's left is to follow it to the best of my ability.
Geto Suguru.
A special-grade curse user who uses Curse Manipulation.
He can draw in and manipulate
naturally occurring unbound curses.
It seems he's established a religious group
to collect curses from its followers.
He should still have the curses he previously possessed,
and considering the recent decline in the number of curses reported,
his claim to possess two thousand may not be a bluff.
Even so, statistically speaking, most of them have to be weaklings at second grade or lower.
And even with a generous estimate,
there can't be much more than fifty curse users.
That's actually the scary part.
I find it hard to believe he'd start a war he couldn't win.
God damn!
Put out a call for aid to all alumni.
Alert the Three Great Clans and the Ainu Jujutsu Society.
It's all-out war!
This time, we will exorcise this curse named Geto!
That's probably what the muscle-brained principal is saying right now.
If we seriously tried to kill each other,
our chance of success would be about thirty percent.
If the Jujutsu Society gets involved,
that goes down to less than twenty percent.
However, there is one move
that makes that slim chance of victory
jump straight to ninety-nine percent.
That is to kill Okkotsu Yuta and take the special-grade vengeful spirit, Orimoto Rika.
They completely bought my bluff back there.
It doesn't matter if the cursed spirit is bound or not,
as long as I'm the one who kills the master,
I can absorb any curse I want.
With such high odds of victory,
they won't risk putting Okkotsu on the battlefield.
After all, there is a chance
he could wipe out both enemies and allies.
The true objective of the Night Parade of a Hundred Demons is to isolate Okkotsu.
At long last, it's the dawn of a new age.
It seems like...
something crazy is going down.
Maki!
What are you doing here?
Classes are canceled for the week.
Well, I just felt kinda restless.
Nobody's at the dorms, either.
The second-years were dispatched to Kyoto earlier.
Toge is in Shinjuku, along with the third- and fourth-years as backup.
And since the principal likes Panda so much, he's probably with Toge.
I see.
Ask away.
Huh?
You've been wondering, right?
About why I'm called a failure.
Well, um... yes.
My family, the Zenin clan, is one of the elite sorcerer families known as the Three Great Clans.
Do you know what's the minimum requirement to be a sorcerer?
Uh, I'm not sure.
It's being able to see curses.
Oh, right.
Ordinary people can sometimes see them in certain situations, like if they're on the verge of death,
but I can't see curses without these lame glasses.
The cursed tools I use are
already infused with cursed energy.
It doesn't come from me.
It gave me a good excuse to get out of the family.
The food was awful, the rooms were cramped, and it was crawling with old men I didn't know.
The whole thing totally sucked!
Don't use my last name!
Not everyone has resistance to curses like you.
Don't ask me about cursed energy.
Why did you continue being a sorcerer, then?
Because I've got a personality problem.
I can't wait to see their reactions
when someone who can't even see curses becomes a first-grade sorcerer.
After that, I'll crush the Zenin clan from within!
What?
Oh, I was just thinking that's so like you.
You know...
I wish I could be just like you.
I want to be strong and unyielding.
I wish I had never given birth to you.
You're the stain on the Zenin clan!
All of you...
make sure you don't turn out like Maki.
If there's anything I can do to help, let me know!
Let's crush the Zenin clan! Maybe.
Moron. There's no point if I don't do it by myself.
I'm going back to my room.
Okay. Later!
I'm such an idiot.
Don't go thinking you've been recognized or something!
Emerge from the darkness that is darker than black.
Purify that which is impure.
A Veil was drawn over the school?
By who? And why?
Keep the collateral damage to a minimum.
There's a chance some civilians still haven't evacuated.
If you find any, get them outta here.
Are you listening, Satoru?
There's one guy who looks like trouble.
I see. That guy with the bandages.
Yes. We'll take on the rest.
I've said this before but—
Yea, I know.
We're only stalling them, right?
Let's take it slow and have some fun
until Geto finishes his job.
You're here?
That a problem?
What the hell are you doing here?
Sorry, but I don't have time to chat with monkeys.
Mr. Gojo!
I have a report!
What's the matter?
Well...
That show-off isn't at the front lines?
Is he in Kyoto?
We would've received a word if he was.
It's nothing. What's up?
I know this isn't the best time,
but I thought it wise to speak up sooner.
It's about the investigation
into Okkotsu that you requested.
Panda! Toge!
What's the—
No questions!
I'm sending you two to Jujutsu Tech right now!
Wha?!
Geto is at the school right now.
I'm absolutely, probably, certain!
Which is it?!
If my intuition is correct,
in the worst case, Yuta and Maki could both die!
I'll head there as soon as I'm done with that foreigner.
Until then, I'm afraid you'll have to
defend them with your lives.
Right!
Salmon!
No way. They figured it out?
This is why I said you should at least prepare a stand-in.
A half-assed dummy would only make things worse.
That's what Master Geto said.
Mimiko, Nanako!
What's up?
We're stepping up the plan. Engage.
I've been waiting for this!
Your opponent is over here, special grade.
Sorry, it's just...
I'm kind of in a hurry right now.
There's a Veil around the school!
Satoru's intuition was right?
I'll break through it!
Then we'll take the shortest route!
Pollack roe!
Oh?
Someone broke through the Veil.
Nothing ever goes quite as planned.
It should take them about five minutes to get here.
Should I ignore them or should I deal with them?
Tough choice.
Did they break through the walls to take the shortest route?
Not bad.
Maki!
Pay attention.
He's good at close combat too?
Oh?
How predictable.
Because it was a feint.
Drumming Beat!
Boy, that was a close one.
Oh, I couldn't agree more.
Plummet!
Toge! You okay?
Caviar.
Yeah, Maki comes first.
Maki, are you okay?
Maki?
Mustard leaf.
N-Not yet...
Another quake?
What is going on?
Amazing.
This is wonderful!
I am incredibly touched right now!
You all raced down here to save Okkotsu, correct?
Sorcerers sacrificing themselves for a fellow sorcerer!
Such affection! Such admiration!
The world I long for is right before my very eyes!
Maki?
To be honest, I wanted you to live, Okkotsu.
But this is all for the future of the jujutsu world.
Panda...
Yuta...
Inumaki...
Run... away...
Come, Rika!
I'm going to kill you.
I'll murder you!
Let's start with quantity over quality.
What's your move, Queen of Curses?
Rika.
These three are horribly wounded. Especially Maki.
I won't let you die!
No fair, no fair!
It's always you, always you!
What are you doing, Rika?
I owe her my life.
Handle her gently, as if she were the most delicate thing in the world!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Don't be mad.
I'm not mad.
Don't hate me.
I won't. Don't worry.
He is our enemy.
Yuta, do you hate him?
Yeah, I loathe him.
Then I hate him, too!
Welcome back.
Why did you stop attacking?
Healing requires an advanced reverse cursed technique.
It was convenient for me to have you focused over there.
Let us start anew from where we left off.
Rika, we're using that.
Snake Eyes and Fangs?
Those are the cursed seals of the Inumaki clan!
Die.
Magnificent!
Cursed speech is an advanced technique passed down in the Inumaki clan.
And yet this young man pulled it off with less than a year of jujutsu training!
That really is complicated.
The scattering of cursed energy makes it hard to aim.
Inumaki is amazing.
Orimoto Rika is an ever-evolving mystery.
A spirit of endless cursed energy.
Yeah...
My friends are amazing.
And you... you dare...
I want her even more.
I'll beat you to a pulp!
Why'd Mr. Nanami have to go to Kyoto?
I wanted him to see me shine!
Shut yer face!
Quit griping and start fighting!
There's more of 'em coming!
Man, such a drag.
That makes fifty.
I've cleared the bare-minimum requirements for the reward.
Might as well work a bit more and aim for the bonus.
How old are you two?
Fifteen.
You're still just children.
It's not too late for you to turn back.
You can't even tell right from wrong yet.
Cringe!
Mimiko, isn't that guy, like, totally annoying?
Shall we hang him, Nanako?
You people have no idea, do you?
You don't know how sorcerers are treated
out in the damn sticks that aren't even on maps.
Right and wrong? Keep that shit to yourselves.
If Master Geto says black is white, then that is that.
We believe in the world he envisions.
Anyone who gets in his way...
...will hang!
Huh?!
Miguel? What are you doing?!
Can't you see?
You're tough.
That rope...
It has an unusual curse woven into it.
It's disrupting my technique.
I barely have half left.
How many decades do you think it took
my country's sorcerers to weave this Black Rope?
Don't care.
One second of my time will outmatch it.
Dummy!
That's all it's worth.
Get lost.
Not good! Mr. Gojo has snapped!
So this is the Limitless technique Geto mentioned.
A precise manipulation of cursed energy at an atomic level
that allows its user to distort space and time at will.
And what makes it all possible is the power of those eyes.
Just over twelve more minutes until my quota is up.
I'll keep fighting for my life!
Wow!
That last round was dangerous.
I should focus on hit-and-runs.
Gotta give everything I got to endure these last ten minutes.
If I die tonight, I'm cursing you, Geto!
Miss Ieiri, please look at this one, too.
I will. Set him down over there.
Right!
What were you all doing?
It's all right.
Miss Ieiri will fix you up.
We're counting on you!
Sheesh.
You really dumped a heap of trouble on us, Geto.
It's the first time you've felt such violent emotions.
Your body must be coursing with cursed energy.
Heightening your physical strength as if you were omnipotent.
Your senses must be sharpened, too.
The riffraff are no longer a match for you.
I'll have to crush you myself.
Follow my lead, Rika.
Despite standing at the top of the food chain,
humans decided to make up the existence of higher beings called gods.
Laughable, isn't it?
Considering us sorcerers already exist.
In the end, those monkeys just don't want
to admit the existence of us superior beings.
You want to be god? Grow up already!
You're missing the point, Okkotsu.
What I long for isn't enlightenment. It's a chosen people.
The weak bury the strong due to sheer numbers.
And the audacity of the monkeys who do that makes me so sick I could vomit.
Yuta, Yuta...
It's all right. I'm getting a hang of it.
Are we done debating?
He's even faster!
Shouldn't have done that.
If you infuse a curse too strong too fast,
the vessel won't handle it.
Satoru didn't teach you that?
You infuse it bit by—
Not bad.
I don't know, dammit!
I don't know about other sorcerers outside of school.
So I don't know if you're right or wrong!
But if I want to stay with my friends...
If I want to believe that I'm allowed to live...
I have no choice but to kill you!
Kinda selfish, don't you think?
Nonetheless, it's all for self-affirmation.
There's nothing more important in life.
In which case, I'll also use all I have to kill you.
No compromises on either quantity or quality.
Did you know?
There are only four humans
crowned with the title of special grade.
Among curses, however, there are sixteen.
This is one of those sixteen.
Special-Grade Mythical Vengeful Spirit: Tamamo Mae!
On top of that, I'll combine the 4,461 curses in my possession into one
and strike you with it.
Curse Manipulation Technique Maximum:
Maelstorm.
Mr. Nanami.
Leave it to me.
New Shadow Style: Simple Domain!
Quick Draw!
Don't let your guard down, Miwa!
Mechamaru, above you!
You should take your own advice.
Everyone, stay alert.
Kamo.
Seven cursed spirits at two o'clock.
Roger that. What is Todo's location?
Oh, I think you'll see him soon enough.
Where have you been all this time, Todo?
Wh-What is that absurd amount of cursed energy?
That one's dangerous, Todo!
Don't rush in on your own!
Wait for back—
The talk show's Christmas special at eight will be hosting Takada!
I can't waste any more time here!
Todo!
Kamo.
More than ten cursed spirits approaching from six o'clock.
Everyone, prepare to intercept!
Jeez, there's no end to them.
How long is this gonna go on?
Okkotsu.
I'm truly glad I came to kill you
before you could fully wield Orimoto Rika.
It's a promise.
When we grow up, we'll get married.
Sure!
Then we'll be together forever and ever!
Rika.
Yes?
Thank you for protecting me all this time.
Thank you for loving me.
Could you lend me your power one last time?
I want to stop him.
I don't need anything else after that.
I'll give you my future, my heart, my body, everything.
From now on, we'll truly be together forever.
I love you, Rika.
Let's die together.
Yuta! Yuta!
I love, love, love you so much!
Sacrificing himself to surpass the limit on her cursed energy?!
I never realized you were such a womanizer!
How rude.
This is pure love.
Then this is justice!
Magnificent!
Absolutely incredible!
Truly the power to change the world!
If I had Rika, there would be no need to sneak around gathering curses.
Next time.
Next time, she will be mine!
You finally made it, Satoru.
To think you'd be the one here at my end.
Is my family safe?
Every last one of them managed to get away.
The ones in Kyoto were also under you, right?
Yeah.
Unlike you, I'm a kind man.
You sent those two assuming I'd defeat them.
All just to trigger Okkotsu's growth.
I trusted you.
Trusted that a man of principle such as you
wouldn't kill off young sorcerers for no reason.
Trust, huh?
I didn't know you still had something like that left for me.
Give this back to him, will you?
Was the elementary school your doing, too?
You guessed it.
I can't believe you.
Do you have any last words?
I'll always hate those monkeys, no matter what.
But I never held any hatred for those at Jujutsu Tech.
I just couldn't wear a heartfelt smile in this world.
Suguru.
At least hit me with some curses at the end.
Yuta! Yuta!
Hey! Wake up!
Hey!
Hey, Yuta, are you okay?!
Mustard leaf.
Wake up already, Yuta!
Oh, he's awake.
You guys...
Are you okay, Maki?
And you, Inumaki?
Wait! Panda, your arm isn't healed!
Oh, chill out.
We're in better shape than you right now.
Unlike these two, my arm can be replaced later.
Thanks for saving us.
Salmon.
Yuta.
I'm sorry, Rika. I didn't mean to keep you waiting.
What's the matter, Yuta?
Well, uh...
In exchange for her power, I kinda p-promised to go with Rika.
What?!
Don't you know that means death?!
What were you thinking, dumbass?!
Uh, well, I...
Huh?
Rika.
Congratulations.
You managed to break the curse.
Who are you?
I'm your good-looking guy, Gojo Satoru!
The theory Yuta came up with sounded interesting,
so I requested an investigation into their families.
The investigation of Rika's was finished a long time ago,
but Yuta's was quite the search.
And then it came to light.
You're a descendant of Sugawara Michizane!
That makes us super-distant relatives!
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yuta, Yay!
Suga—
Uh, who?
One of Japan's Three Great Vengeful Spirits!
Dude's a super-big-shot sorcerer!
Tuna!
You were right, Yuta.
Rika didn't place a curse on you.
You placed a curse on Rika.
Rika...
What do I do?! Is she going to die?! I have to save her!
Don't die! Don't die! Don't die! Don't die! Don't die!
Oh right...
Back then, I rejected Rika's death.
Now the curser has canceled the bond.
As long as the cursed doesn't seek retribution against you, the curse will be broken.
Though, I guess that much was obvious
after seeing her like that.
It was all my fault.
I turned you into a curse.
I hurt all those people.
Everyone nearly died because Geto came after me!
It's all...
It's all my...
Yuta.
Thank you.
For giving me more time
and letting me stay by your side.
These past six years,
I've been happier than I ever was while alive.
Bye-bye. Take care.
And don't come over too soon, okay?
Okay.
See you later!
It's a bit late, but you weren't
at fault for the incident with Geto.
He would've come to attack Jujutsu Tech
whether you were here or not.
You think so?
Also, here.
Oh, my student ID.
You found it for me, Sir?
No, not me.
My best friend did.
The only one I had.
Come on, Yuta!
How long are you gonna keep us waiting?
Let's go!
Yeah!
This is yum.
Ain't it?
I used this spice called Royco.
Gives it a nice flavor.
Royco is the magic powder
that makes everything taste Kenyan.
More importantly, they really went home, right?
Yeah.
For that, I'm happy.
This really is good. Reminds me of nikujaga.
What was that?
Call it beef stew, my man!
Something wrong?
What are you doing here?
Oh?
Sir?
Hey. Been a while.